let questions = [{
    "question": "1. Which of these is not a logical operator?",
    "option1": "&&",
    "option2": "!",
    "option3": "!!",
    "option4": "||",
    "answer": "!!"
}, {
    "question": "2. Which of the following methods combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
    "option1": "add()",
    "option2": "merge()",
    "option3": "concat()",
    "option4": "append()",
    "answer": "concat()"
}, {
    "question": "3. Which of the following methods does not return a new array?",
    "option1": "forEach()",
    "option2": "map()",
    "option3": "filter()",
    "option4": "every()",
    "answer": "forEach()"
}, {
    "question": "4. Which is not a primitive data type in JavaScript?",
    "option1": "Boolean",
    "option2": "Null",
    "option3": "Character",
    "option4": "Undefined",
    "answer": "Character"
}, {
    "question": "5. What character ends a JavaScript statement?",
    "option1": ":",
    "option2": ".",
    "option3": ";",
    "option4": ",",
    "answer": ";"
}, {
    "question": "6. Is JavaScript case sensitive?",
    "option1": "No",
    "option2": "Yes",
    "option3": "May be?",
    "option4": "Not sure!",
    "answer": "Yes"
}, {
    "question": "7. What does 3+4+'7' evaluate to?",
    "option1": "14",
    "option2": "7",
    "option3": "77",
    "option4": "error",
    "answer": "77"
}, {
    "question": "8. What looping structures are there in JavaScript?",
    "option1": "for",
    "option2": "while",
    "option3": "do-while",
    "option4": "all of them",
    "answer": "all of them"
}, {
    "question": "9. If the submit button on a form is clicked which event handler is invoked?",
    "option1": "onsubmit",
    "option2": "onclick",
    "option3": "onload",
    "option4": "ispostback",
    "answer": "onsubmit"
}, {
    "question": "10. Which method changes the contents of an array by removing existing elements and/or adding new elements?",
    "option1": "sort()",
    "option2": "splice()",
    "option3": "unsplice()",
    "option4": "unshift()",
    "answer": "splice()"

}];